Weiner, David Papers 5968
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
David Weiner Papers
1962-1994
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Weiner, David
5968
15 cubic feet
15 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
5743730
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, September 17, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 18, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Teachers' unions; Teachers' unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Weiner, David; United Federation of Teachers
5743730
- Contracts - UFT Exec. Bd. 1990-94. (Box 1)
  - United Federation of Teachers Contracts: 1962-1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - United Federation of Teachers Contracts: 1972-1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - United Federation of Teachers Contracts: 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - United Federation of Teachers contract: 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - United Federation of Teachers Contracts: 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - United Federation of Teachers Contracts: 1987-1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - United Federation of Teachers: Proposed Salary Schedules; Articles (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - United Federation of Teachers: Late 1980s (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - United Federation of Teachers: 1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - United Federation of Teachers: Jan.-June 1991 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - United Federation of Teachers: July and August 1991 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - United Federation of Teachers: Sept.-Dec. 1991 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - United Federation of Teachers: Jan.-May 1992 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - United Federation of Teachers: June-Dec. 1992 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - United Federation of Teachers: Jan.-April 1993 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - United Federation of Teachers: May-Dec. 1993 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - United Federation of Teachers: 1994 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Decentralization. (Box 2)
  - Districts - MIJL Local School Boards (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Draft/Military Registration (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Eastern District High School, Brooklyn, NY (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Decentralization - Community Control (NY) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Decentralization of NY Schools Info. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Community Control - NY (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Schools Policies and Integration (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Pro-Decentralization Organizations (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - United Federation of Teachers (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Other Organizations Statements and Materials (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 1964 Community Control Legislature Committee Information (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - New York Times Community Control/Decentralization Articles (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Decentralization Proposed Plans/Case Study (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Decentralization Policy Information (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Decentralization Articles and Reports (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Decentralization Articles and Reports Continued (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Decentralization; Union elections. (Box 3)
  - People Change Schools - Practical Agenda (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Governing the NYC Schools - Report of the Board (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - NYC Community School District Decentralization Laws (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - NYC Community School District Boundary Lines (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Improving the Odds: Making Decentralization Work for Children, Schools and Communities (Nov. 1987) (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Temporary State Commission on NYC School Governance (April 1991) (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - NYC Decentralization Information (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Community Control Decentralization (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Integration (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - 1991 - Election Notices - Ballots (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - United Federation of Teachers (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - 1991 Unity Literature (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Election of 1991 - Zemsky GDRI Letter, etc. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - 1989 NY Election, Election Results (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - 1987 United Federation of Teachers Election (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - United Federation of Teachers Election 1983 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - 1981 United Federation of Teachers Elections (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - 1979 United Federation of Teachers Election (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Union elections. (Box 4)
  - 1977 United Federation of Teachers Election (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 1975 United Federation of Teachers Election (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 1974 United Federation of Teachers Election (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 1973 United Federation of Teachers Election (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 1971 United Federation of Teachers Election (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 1970 United Federation of Teachers Election (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 1969 United Federation of Teachers Election (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Collective Bargaining (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - The United Teacher Special Election Issue - 1967 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Official UTF Election Bulletin 1967 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - General UFT Election Information (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - 1981 AAA - Ms. Elvira Robbins (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Shilman Election 1985 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - United Federation of Teachers Elections (various) (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - 1985 Election - Appeal Arbitration 2nd Election (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - 1991 Election Challenge (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Elections - Local School Board (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Elections up to 1976 - City, State, and Federal (Box 4, Folder 18)
- A-B. (Box 5)
  - Affirmative Action Title 7 - Labor (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Affirmative Action in the 1980s (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - AFT (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - AFT and the CIA (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - AFT 1990 Boston Convention (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - AIDS (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Report and Articles on Failing Schools (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Alternative Programs in Schools (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Academic Freedom (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Accountability (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Affirmative Action Quotas (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - DA - 1980-81 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - AFT Convention: July 1983 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Advocates for Children (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - AFT Convention 1982 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Agency Shop (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Bankruptcy Takeovers (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Bennett (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Bilingualism (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Bill of Rights - Civil Liberties (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Black Americans (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Black History - M.L. King (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Board of Education (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Capital Budget Briefs (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Chapter Chairs Handbook (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Executive Budgets - Brief (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - NYC Teacher Union Tentative Budget Briefs (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - NYC Board of Education Budgets (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Business and the Schools (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Busing (Box 5, Folder 30)
- B-C. (Box 6)
  - Baird-Jefferson (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - New York City Board of Examiners (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Statement (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Bilingual Education (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - School Transportation - Busing (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Integration 1973 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Teacher Certification Articles (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Committee Against Racism National Report (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Arbitration Award - LOBA 1984-87 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - City University of New York (CUNY) - General College (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Educational Issues 1 - Class Size (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Contract 1985, etc. (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Consumer Problems (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Drugs/Drug Education (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - DeFunis Articles (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Constitutions and Revisions (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Contract 1980-81 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Contract Negotiations 1978 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - General Information for - Contract of 1972 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Contract 1975-77: Memorandum, Ratification, Ballot (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - 1975 Contract - Vote No (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Contract Deferral 1977 Addendum (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Contract Addendum to 1977-78 and 1978-80 Contract (Box 6, Folder 23)
- C-D. (Box 7)
  - NYC School Districts Calendars (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Substitutes (CPT and CPP) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Career Ladder - Merit Pay (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Censorship (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Chancellor (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Chapter Elections (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Charter - A School (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Children (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Choice of Enrollment Vouchers (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Civil Rights Board of Education (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Class Size (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Collective Bargaining (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - College Admissions, etc. (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Columbus (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Community School Districts (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Constitutions (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Constitution cont. (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Contract 81-84 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - COPE (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Corporal Punishment (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Corridor Initiative (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Corruption (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Court Rulings on Teachers and Students Articles (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Curriculum (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - United Federation of Teachers Delegate Assembly 1993-94 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - United Federation of Teachers Delegate Assembly 1992-93 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - United Federation of Teachers Delegate Assembly 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - United Federation of Teachers Delegate Assembly 1990-91 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - United Federation of Teachers Delegate Assembly 1989-90 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - United Federation of Teachers Delegate Assembly 1988-89 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - United Federation of Teachers Delegate Assembly 1982-84 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - People's Daily World (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - United Federation of Teachers Delegate Assembly 1982-88 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Decentralization and Budget Allocations (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Discipline (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Discrimination - 1977 - Civil Rights Proceedings (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Dropouts (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Dues (Box 7, Folder 38)
- E-F, H-N. (Box 8)
  - ED for Democracy (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - United Federation of Teachers - Summary of UFT Irregularities (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - EIT (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Feldman Articles (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Elections Chapter (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - E.S.R. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Federal Articles (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Higher Education (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Holocaust (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Homebound (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Homosexuals Teaching (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Integration NYC (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Integration and Segregation (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - IQ Tests (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Jewish Labor Committee (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Learning Disability - Behavior Modification (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - License Requirements - Mannix Decision (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Local School Boards (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - School Board Elections 1975 and 1977 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Macchiarola (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - May Day (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Minority Teachers and Students (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous (Farm Prices) (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Moynihan (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - National Caucus of Labor Committees (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - N.E.A. (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - N.E.A. Project NY Disaffiliation 1976 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - NYC Facts and Figures (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - New York State United Teachers (NYSUT) and United Teachers of New York (UTNY) (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - New York State United Teachers (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - PARAS (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - State Aid Parochial Private (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Pellicano (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Proportional Representation (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Quotas (Box 8, Folder 35)
- F-P. (Box 9)
  - NYC Schools Financials (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Foreigners and Education (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Gay and Lesbian (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Green (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Guidance Counselors (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Higher Horizons (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Head Start (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Homeless (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Hurwitz, Howard (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Injury in the Line of Duty (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Illiteracy (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Integration (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Shanker Articles (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Martin Luther King and Black History (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Ku Klux Klan (KKK) Information (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Election of Officers (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Learning Alliance (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Legal (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Legislation (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Lengthening School Year (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Letter Boxes (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Licensing (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Literacy (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Local School Boards (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Longer School Day/Year (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Math and Science (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Extended Use of School Buildings (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Mentor (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Merging (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Merit Pay (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Migrant Children (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Military Leave - Service in Schools (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Minority Children and Teachers (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Minority Statistics (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Misc. (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Multicultural (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - NEA (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - NAC 1988-89 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - NYSUT (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Officers Salaries (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Organizations (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - PARAS (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Peer Review and Intervention (Box 9, Folder 43)
- P-S. (Box 10)
  - Privatization (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Professionalism (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Racism (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Literacy - Reading in Schools (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Reagan and Education (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Real Reform (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Reform - 1988 Election (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Religion (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - ROTC (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Salaries and Contingency Pay (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Salary (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Salaries Positions (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Salaries; Working Conditions (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Salary 1969-76 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Salaries (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Salaries 1962 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Salaries Cont. (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - SBM/SDM (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Scandals and Corruption (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - School Options (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Sex Ed. (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Secretaries (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Segregation (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Racism Articles (Box 10, Folder 24)
- S-W. (Box 11)
  - Special Ed (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Special Items (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Statistics - Children (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Education Statistics (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Strikes (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Students (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Substitutes (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Summit (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Supervisors and Administrators (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Surveys (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Taylor Law (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Teachers (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Teachers Choice High School (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Tenure (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Testing (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Tolerance (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Transfer Plan (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - UAC (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - UFT (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - UFT Annual Statements (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - UFT Committees (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - UFT Welfare Fund (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Violence in Schools (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Vouchers (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Wall Charts (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Welfare (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Miscellaneous. (Box 12)
  - Arbitration Articles (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Student Turmoil (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Student's Rights (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Substitutes (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Substitute Secretary (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Supervisor Selecting (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Suspensions (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Suspensions (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Tenure (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Testing and Test Scores (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Competency Testing (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Tuition Tax Credits (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - UHC (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - UFT NYSUT 1978-79 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - UFT NYSUT (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - UFT 1983 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Volunteers (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Voucher Performances (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Welfare and UFT Benefits for Members (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Bulletin Board/General NYC Education Info/Articles (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Reading and Illiteracy (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Recertification (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - AFT Referenda (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Residency (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Sabbatical (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - School Aides - DC 37 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - School Funding and Budgets (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - School Secretaries (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Scribner (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Seniority and Layoffs (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Statistic (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Teachers - Strikes up to 1952 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Strikes 1978 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Strikes - Sept. 1975 - 5 Days (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Miscellaneous. (Box 13)
  - NYC School Union Newspapers and Bulletins (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Teacher's for Community Control and Teacher's Action Caucus (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Teacher's Action Committee Bulletins (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Teachers for Community Control (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Teachers for Community Control and Teacher's Action Committee (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - LOBA 1985 Arbitration (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - HEW-OCR Memorandum of Agreement 1977 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Grievances (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - UFT 1972 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Financing Schools (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Financial Statements (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Paula Friedman - PS 115 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Fuentes District 1 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Funding (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Education in Foreign Countries - Cuba and USSR (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - EPP (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Federal Aid (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Finance (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Education - Miscellaneous (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Education Policy Issues (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - High School Diploma (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Eastern District High School (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Strike 1967 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Students - College (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Miscellaneous. (Box 14)
  - "From Risk to Renewal" (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Dropouts (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Education Reports and Recommendations (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Reform TAC (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Education Reports 1983-84 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Action Plan Regents (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Bicentennial of Board of Regents: 1983-85 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Misassignment of Teachers, "The Revolution that is Overdue" and Experimental School Organization Plan (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - "Children in Need" (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - "Condoms in the Schools" (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - "A Nation Prepared: Teachers for the 21st Century" (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Putting Professionalism Back into Teaching (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - "Time for Results: The Governors' 1991 Report on Education" (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - "The New York Report: A Blueprint for Learning and Teaching" (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - "A Nation at Risk" (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - "Educational Progress: Cities Mobilize to Improve Their Schools" (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - "What Works: Schools Without Drugs" (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - "What Works: Research About Teaching and Learning" (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - "Failing Students - Failing Schools" (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - "An Imperiled Generation: Saving Urban Schools" (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - "What Works: Educating Disadvantaged Children" (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - "Investing in our Children" (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - A Briefing Book on the Status of American Children in 1988 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - "First Lessons: A Report on Elementary Education in America" (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Segregation Articles (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - "A Nation Prepared: Teachers for the 21st Century" (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Miscellaneous. (Box 15)
  - NYC School Decentralization (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - School Policy in NYC (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - "Community Issues" and School Decentralization (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Reports (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Education Articles (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - "School Boards: Strengthening Grassroots Leadership" (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Desegregation and Humanities in Public Schools (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - School Budget and Business (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Educated Children Reports (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Racial Isolation in the Public Schools (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - The Report of the Commission on the Year 2000 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Educational Reports (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Academic Tracking and Choosing a School (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - 1989 Annual Report (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - "Education That Works: An Action Plan for the Education of Minorities" (Box 15, Folder 15)